<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Nino Müller Dataverse</title><link>https://ninomueller.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nino Müller Dataverse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:42:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ninomueller.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Engineering Skills 2022</title><link>https://ninomueller.com/posts/data-engineering-skills-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:42:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ninomueller.com/posts/data-engineering-skills-2022/</guid><description>One of my tasks at Substring is to always scout for technology trends to find out what technologies help our clients most to reach their target to become Data-driven. The tech field for fats engineers is huge and evolving fast.
I put together a short list of tech skills that I think data engineers in 2022 should master to give as much value to clients as possible. Obviously there is a load of so called soft skills needed as well.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Opensource Datawarehouse for a Small Company</title><link>https://ninomueller.com/posts/creating-an-opensource-datawarehouse-for-a-small-company/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:23:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ninomueller.com/posts/creating-an-opensource-datawarehouse-for-a-small-company/</guid><description>In my company Substring - The Data Company we decided to become more data-driven and wanted to set up a simple data warehouse for our every day business. We decided to set up everything with open source software and wanted to host it in our own Kubernetes cluster.
Open source DWH stack Our stack for this data warehouse is quite simple: Data Ingestion Meltano has made Data ingestion for many SaaS applications a hell lot easier.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://ninomueller.com/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:28:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ninomueller.com/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello World Hi, My name is Nino Müller! 👋
I am a Data Engineer, Software Developer and Entrepreneur in Switzerland working for Substring - The Data Company. This is my personal blog project to write down some of my learnings and projects around #dataengineering #softwaredevelopment #dataengineering #opensource #elt #dwh and many more data and software topics. Not sure what else I will blog about, let&amp;rsquo;s see.</description></item></channel></rss>